This will be the final boarding call for flight to London, Heathrow.
I'm not even gonna say it, Kate.
Then it'll be like I never left.
Wait.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
About the plane? You think it's gonna crash? Don't say that.
No. Look, I know that we've talked about this a thousand times
and we agreed that going to London was the right thing to do.
But in my heart...this feels wrong.
Don't go, Jack.
You mean don't go at all?
Well, what...what about my internship?
Believe me, I know...I know what an incredible opportunity this is for you.
For us, Kate.
Right, for us.
But I'm afraid that if you get on that plane...Look.
We're at the airport. Nobody ever thinks clearly at the airport.
So we should just trust the decision we already made.
You've been accepted to one of the best law schools in the country.
I've got this internship at Barclay's Bank. We have a great plan, honey.
You wanna do something great, Jack?
Let's flush the plan.
Let's start our lives right now, today.
I mean, I have no idea what this life is gonna look like
but I know that it has the both of us in it
and I choose us.
The plan doesn't make us great, Jack.
What we have together, that's what makes us great.
I love you, Kate.
I love you too. I do.
And one year in London is not gonna change that.
A hundred years couldn't change that.
Last night was incredible. Huh?
I said, last night was great.
You are an amazing lover.
Thanks.
You're not bad yourself.
I wanna see you again.
I'd like that too.
Tonight.
It's Christmas eve, Jack.
So? I'll pour eggnog over you.
I have to go visit my parents out in Jersey.
Jersey?
Do you have any idea what the traffic's gonna be like?
That's why I'm taking the train.
It was nice meeting you, Jack.
Mrs.Peterson.
Hello, Jack.
You don't have to stop singing on my account.
Oh, it's because I'm shy, Betty.
So, when are you gonna leave that old corpse, Mr.Peterson, and run away with me?
You know you could never satisfy me the way he does.
Merry Christmas, Mr.Campbell.
How'd you make out this year, Tony?
About four grand
and a bottle of 25-year-old Scotch from 9D.
I'm putting it all in commercial paper like you said.
Good, but just until the deutsche mark turns.
- Thank you, Mr.Campbell.  - All right.
Good morning, Joe.
Merry Christmas, sir.
Campbell wants these available.
Thanks, Adelle.
Better you than me.
If MedTech shares fall any lower than 43
we're in trouble with the stock valuations.
So for God's sake, please watch what you say to your institutional customers.
We still have almost a full day of trading before zero hour
and I don't want any trouble.
A penny for your thoughts, Alan.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
Jack, I was thinking about, you know, Dee and the kids. I promised I'd be home for dinner.
It's Christmas eve, Jack.
Oh, is that tonight?
You think I like being here on Christmas eve, Alan?
No.
Well, maybe.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I do have a touch of tunnel vision this holiday season.
But in two days we're going to announce...
one of the largest mergers in U.S. corporate history.
When a deal like this turns up, you get on it and you ride it till it's over.
You don't ask it for a vacation.
December 26.
After that there'll be so much money floating around here, it'll be like Christmas every day.
December 26, people. If you'd like to celebrate that day
you all have my blessing.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I don't want you to be sorry. I want you to be excited.
I want my gift to you to be the first gift you open this year.
You know why?
Because my gift comes with ten zeroes.
You're right. I'm focused. I'm there.
Good man. Everybody, turn to page 12 in your prospectus.
You have six messages. Two of them are imperative.
Whoa. I'm going home. I'm not even here now. Good night.
- Merry Christmas.  - Merry Christmas.
It's only 8:30. I'm disappointed. Got some last-minute shopping to do?
You too? This holiday's about giving.
I'm giving everything I've got to this deal.
So in a way, I'm more Christmassy than anybody.
You're my role model, Jack.
Oh, and Oxford called.
My suits are ready.
Care for a Lifesaver?
No, thank you.
Help yourself.
Kate Reynolds.
Her assistant said you could reach her at home after 8:00.
Kate Reynolds was my girlfriend in college.
I almost married her.
You? Married?
Almost married.
And almost a broker at E.F.Hutton.
Excuse me?
She didn't want me to go to London.
We're standing at the airport saying good-bye
and she asked me to stay.
So you left her.
Wasn't easy.
Oh, stop it. I'm getting all weepy.
I took the road less traveled, Adelle.
And look where it took ya.
I'm gonna get this gal on the phone.
Nope.
You almost married this woman.
You're not even curious why she called?
She's probably just having a fit of nostalgia. Lonely Christmas eve.
Called the one that got away.
Why call her back and mislead her?
This happened a very, very long time ago.
8:35 on Christmas eve.
Jack Campbell still at his desk.
Now there's a Hallmark moment for you.
Peter
I don't see you rushing home to trim the tree.
That's because I'm a heartless bastard who only cares about money.
Well, you know what? God love you for that.
Got a call from Terry Haight.
Bob Thomas is nervous.
That'll happen when you're about to spend $130 billion on some aspirin.
Somebody's gotta nurse him through this.
Why are you staring at my breasts, Peter?
I need you, tiger.
Where is he?
Aspen.
Call Aunt Irma and tell her I won't be able to make it.
You're a credit to capitalism, Jack.
Hey, Peter, let me ask you a question.
An old girlfriend calls you out of the blue on Christmas eve.
What do you do?
You suddenly having trouble getting dates?
Yeah.
Leave it in the past.
Old flames are like old tax returns...
put 'em in the file cabinet for three years, and then you cut 'em loose.
I'll leave from my office tomorrow in the afternoon.
Call the group.
Schedule an emergency strategy session for noon.
That'll be a nice little holiday treat.
Good night, Frank.
Hey, Mr.Campbell.
Why didn't you call down? I would have had Joe get your ride.
I'm thinking I'll walk tonight. It's a nice night for it.
I'll send your car home for you.
That'll be fine.
And Merry Christmas to you, sir.
To you too.
Eggnog?
Yeah, dairy case. Five dollars.
Hey, yo. Y'all do the lotto here, right? Y'all do the lotto here?
Yeah. Cool. 'Cause I got a winner, baby. I got a winner.
Certified, good as gold. I know lotto keep a lot of brothers down, but not Cash Money.
Don't do me none, son, 'cause I'd be like...
Bang on the lottery! You know what I mean? It's all good.
Relax, son. Relax. I got you four numbers. Check it. Bust it.
6, 14, 16, 49. That's a winner, son.
$238, B.Cheddar coming. Give me my money.
I'm sorry. Your ticket is bad.
You draw in the lines.
What are you talking about, B.?
You draw in the lines with a pencil. I know about this.
Yo, buster, check the ticket, son.
No, you get out.
Yo, you ain't even looked at the ticket. You lookin' at me, son. Check the ticket.
You get out now! You take the ticket somewhere else!
Next customer in line!
You get out or I call 9-1-1 .
Oh, my God!
Check the ticket, stupid.
Look at the ticket.
Shit, now I'm gonna make you call God.
That's my word. You best check that ticket, fool!
Let me see the ticket.
Was I talkin' to you?
Maybe I'll buy it from you. You know, make a little business deal.
Stupid-ass white boy in $2,000 suit gets capped trying to be a hero. News at 11:00.
That's what you wanna see? You wanna see Cash up in here? You want me to set it, son?
Do you wanna die?
Do you want to die?
No.
Look, I'm talking about a business deal.
Okay? I buy the ticket from you for $200.
I take it to a store where the guy behind the counter doesn't have a death wish.
I just made myself a quick $38.
Like I said, it's...
it's just a business deal.
All right. Yeah.
All right.
You blew it, B. You blew it.
The ticket was real.
Damn, you had your chance too.
Come on, Jack. Let's get out of here.
How'd you know my name was Jack?
I call all you guys Jack.
Here.
Nice doing business with ya.
What do you want to carry that gun around for anyway?
You're just gonna wind up doing something you regret.
You're talking to the wrong person about regrets, Jack.
I mean, there must be programs out there and, um, opportunities.
Wait a minute.
Are you actually trying to save me?
This is bananas.
This man thinks I need to be saved, yo?
Well, everybody needs something.
Yeah?
Well, what do you need, Jack?
Me?
You just said
everybody needs something.
I got everything I need.
Wow. It must be great being you.
I'm not saying that you'd be able to do it without some hard work, some honest hard work,
and possibly some medicine.
You know, I'm gonna really enjoy this.
You just remember that you did this, Jack, okay?
You brought this on yourself.
Merry Christmas.
Ten more minutes, Jack.
It's Christmas.
Never mind.
Who's here?
Rise and shine.
Don't you think we should open some presents?
- I think you should give Mama five more minutes in bed. - Come on, Dad. Get up.
Yea! It's Christmas! It's Christmas!
Look, your sister's jumping on the bed.
What is this dog doing on the bed? He needs to get off the bed.
Did Santa come?
I don't know. We'll have to go see.
Mommy just needs to wake up.
Jack.
Strong coffee.
Oh, Jack. Merry Christmas, dear.
Lorraine.
Ed.
Hey, Jack, you old bird dog. Merry Christmas to ya.
Talk to him.
One day a year away from the Ponderosa. I don't think that's asking too much.
This is who I am.
Tell her, Jack, for God's sake. You're the only one around here that gets me.
I need some eggnog.
'Course you do, sweet thing. Almost 8:00 in the morning.
Excuse me.
Where you going, Jack?
Josh, Annie, giddyup!
Where's my car? Where's my Ferrari?
Where's my Ferrari?
What the hell are you talking? What's he talking about?
You got a Ferrari?
Let me borrow your car and then I promise I'll have it returned.
My Caddy? Drive your own damn car.
Oh, just let him borrow your precious Cadillac, for God sakes.
There's a perfectly good minivan sitting out there in the driveway. Here.
What the hell's wrong with him anyway?
Tony, thank God!
Sorry, pal. Entrance is for residents and guests only.
What?
What are you talking about?
Jack Campbell, penthouse "C."
What's the matter with you?
Mrs.Peterson, I think there's something wrong with our man Tony here.
Who is this man?
Oh, come on.
What is going on with you two this morning? Is this like a...
a Christmas joke?
Who is this man?
Well, we're on the co-op board together, Betty.
And we fought side by side for garbage disposals.
And every morning we exchange quasi-sexual witty banter.
Okay? Shall I call the cops? I'm gonna call the cops.
No, I'm gonna call the cops!
You're scaring me.
- No, no, no, no. - Thank you for not calling the cops.
Now, I'm going upstairs, I'm gonna get some sleep. Then I'll be fine.
Sleep you shall. Noblesse oblige isn't dead. Not yet anyway.
Let's...let's get you some help. Surely there's a shelter somewhere in this city.
A shelter?
Hey, hey, are you smacked out of your head?
I'm the richest man in this building!
I've got twice the square footage you have!
And I'm going upstairs.
Take a walk, pal.
Oh, not cool.
Not cool!
You wanna get cute? Get cute.
I'm gonna go to my office.
I'm gonna file a complaint to the manager of the building.
I'm gonna have you fired, Tony.
And, Mrs.Peterson
you're on notice with the co-op board!
So you better just stop whatever this is that you're doing!
Oh, come on!
Frank
you won't believe what's been happening to me. Is Adelle here yet?
- Hold it right there.  - Where's Mintz?
The building is closed, pal. You have to come back tomorrow.
Frank
why do I feel the need to remind you that I'm Jack Campbell, President?
I don't care who you are.
It's Christmas, and like I told you, the building is closed.
I don't think you heard me correctly.
I'm Jack Campbell.
Jack Campbell!
President!
Have a nice holiday, man.
That's my car!
Hi, Jack.
You stole my car.
I know this whole thing is really bizarre to you and you're feeling quite shocked
but just hop in. I'll explain everything to you, okay?
Come on.
Come on.
You're probably gonna wanna buckle up, Jack.
This thing moves.
What's happening to me?
Breathe into the bag, Jack.
This kind of thing makes a lot of guys have to throw up. I seen it happen before.
So if you feel the urge, you roll down the window and do it out there.
Try not to get so worked up, Jack.
After all, you brought this on yourself.
Brought what on myself? I didn't do anything!
"I got everything I need."
That sound familiar?
You mean 'cause you thought I was cocky
I'm now on a permanent acid trip?
Bag yourself, Jack.
Oh, my God!
The way you intervened in that store last night, you did a good thing there, Jack.
I mean, it was incredibly impressive all the way across the board to the upper echelons of the organization.
Oh, God! Please just tell me what's happening to me in plain English
without the mumbo-jumbo.
This is a glimpse, Jack.
A glimpse?
I...A glimpse of what?
You're gonna have to figure that out for yourself and you got plenty of time.
How much time?
As much time as it takes which in your case is probably gonna be considerable.
Okay, look, look. I-I-I just want my life back, okay?
Now, what's it gonna take?
You wanna talk turkey? Let's talk turkey.
How much money?
It doesn't work like that, and I can't tell you why.
Why not?
Because you have to figure this thing out for yourself.
Are you listening to me? Figure it out, figure it out. Figure out what?
Let it come to you, man.
I don't have time for this right now. I'm in the middle of a deal.
Well, you're working on a new deal now, baby.
What's this?
Open it.
What is it, some kind of a signal?
Will you come whenever I ring it?
Now you gotta get out of the car, Jack.
But what do I do?
I'm sorry. I can't spend any more time with you.
I got some other business I gotta take care of. No, y-y-you did this to me.
You can't just leave me like this.
Okay.
Look, you wanna get some air?
Let's get outside, get some air. We'll walk and I'll explain everything to you, okay?
Thanks, man.
Sure.
Excuse me. Do you know where Merrison Street is?
Jeannie. I found Jack.
Oh, there you are, stranger.
Where you been?
You look terrible.
Truth is, I expected you.
Kate called and asked if I knew where you were, so...
Oh, I put the Barcalounger in the center of the room. It's throwing everybody off.
What do you think?
It's a great room. Great room.
You and me, buddy, we know how to live, huh?
Come on.
Come on, Jack.
Come on.
Come on, buddy.
Take your seat.
Are you okay?
I mean, you take off Christmas morning and you don't tell anyone where you're going.
We're friends?
Talk to me.
I'm having kind of a bad day.
You know, I read somewhere that the suicide rate doubles during the holiday.
What am I saying that for? You don't wanna hear that. Come on.
Is it...is it trouble at work?
I...I don't think so.
Well, it's not Kate, is it?
You see, huh?
It's like we're inside each other's heads.
Kate's my wife.
Just keep saying it over and over again, Jack, like a mantra. Keep saying it.
Look, you know, you fit the profile exactly in your 30s
house, kids, financial responsibilities.
You start thinking this isn't the life I dreamt about.
Where's the romance, you know?
Where's the joie de vivre?
Suddenly
every lingerie ad in the Newark Star-Ledger represents a life that you can't have.
It's just two kids, right?
Come on. Come on.
All right, sometimes it feels like you gave up the whole world. I know that.
But look what you got. Look at that
four bedrooms, two-and-a-half baths
a partially finished basement.
And good kids. Look. You know what?
You probably don't wanna hear this right now.
But remember last summer
when I almost had that thing with Arnie, Jr.'s speech therapist?
You remember what you said to me?
You said, "Don't screw up the best thing in your life...
just because you're a little unsure about who you are."
Okay?
Go get 'em, tiger.
Could you hold on a second?
Um, never mind because...because he just walked in.
Thank you. Thank you.
Do you...have any idea what you put us through today?
You walk out of here at 7:30 in the morning.
You don't tell me where you're going, or even that you're going.
And I don't see you till hours later?
I called all of our friends. I had the state troopers looking for you.
I was on the phone with the hospital, for God's sakes.
What kind of man leaves his family Christmas morning without a word about where he's going?
What kind of a man does that, Jack?
I don't know.
Could you... could you please stop yelling at me?
Where were you?
I was in the city.
The city?
New York City?
Yeah.
Why?
Because that's where I live.
Don't start, Jack. Don't.
Look, you don't understand.
I-I-I woke up this morning here.
And this is very strange because...
this isn't my house.
And those aren't my kids. I'm not Dad.
I-I-I'm not a dad. You're not my wife.
You know what, Jack. It's not funny this time...
because I am really mad.
I mean, really mad. I mean it. I don't even...
What...what's that?
I like it. Thanks, Dad.
That's mine. Hey, I need that back.
She took my bell.
You missed the whole thing...
the pancakes and the presents.
You spent six hours putting that bike together for Annie
and then you didn't even get to see the look on her face when she opened it.
You missed Christmas, Jack.
I'm sorry.
You know, we don't even have enough time for this.
And at least you're okay. I'm okay, we're okay.
But you've gotta get dressed for the Thompson party. And you are not wearing that.
I don't care how hilarious you think it is.
Party? No, I'm not going to a party.
You look forward to this party all year.
What is it with you today?
Believe me, Kate.
I really don't think that going to a party is the right move for me at the present time.
Okay, fine. You know what? Then you just do whatever you wanna do.
What are you doing?
Telling my mother she doesn't have to stay with the kids.
Why not?
Because you'll be here.
I'll be ready in ten minutes.
This is...
this is just subpar.
Lance, here you go.
Kate. Jack. Evelyn.
Come in.
Hey, everybody, Kate and Jack are here.
Hey! Jeannie.
Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas.
Jack, Merry Christmas.
So, like the dress?
Oh, it's lovely.
I thought I saw you notice it at the kids' recital.
It's lovely. It's lovely.
There he is.
Hey, Jack. Happy holidays, man.
Jack, come on over.
Hey, Jack.
Cheers, baby.
You guys see Van Horn last night?
Thirty-two points.
That kid's gonna take the Nets to the championship.
The Nets? Are you kidding? They suck.
But they're due.
They're certainly due.
So, tomorrow's the big day, Jackie.
Okay.
Why?
My triple bypass. I'm going under the knife tomorrow.
I told you that, right?
Triple bypass. Yeah.
You really think you should be eating all that?
Figure I'm going in for a cleaning tomorrow.
Might as well load up on the fried stuff tonight, right?
That's good thinking, Bill. Have another drink.
Some fried pork, mashed potatoes.
He'll be dead by morning.
How 'bout a cigar, Jack?
Oh, no, thank you. I'm cutting down.
Come on. They're American made, not Cuban.
Oh, really?
Come on.
Very nice.
I thought you'd like 'em.
Superb.
How 'bout you, Arnie?
I'm all right. Thanks.
Finger food?
No, thank you. I'm fine.
Come on.
Soon as I put 'em down, you're gonna grab a couple.
You always do. No, I'm okay.
Let me. They will melt in your mouth.
Yeah.
Good?
Fabulous.
At the end of this whole thing...
she made me this hand-embroidered sweater.
It was really lovely. How nice.
So I'm slipping it on
and I notice that she's misspelled the word "lawyers."
I spent the entire day walking around with a sweater that said
"Nonprofit layers do it for free."
So you're a lawyer?
A nonprofit lawyer?
Probono.
You don't get paid at all? Nobody makes a dime?
Anyhoo...
I better go wake my mom.
There you go.
I don't think so.
She's your dog, Jack.
No, she's not.
You're right. She's the kids' dog.
Maybe we should go wake Josh and make him walk her.
If you take a dump sometime in this century
then we could go home where it's warm.
If I can even remember how to get home.
You remember, don't you, girl?
Hello?
Hello?
Hey!
What?
That baby's crying.
And?
Don't give me that look, Jack.
Tuesday's your day and you know it.
And listen, try and get Josh to day care on time, okay?
Yeah. All right.
Holy Mother of God!
You're not really my dad, are you?
No, I'm not.
I work on Wall Street
you know, with the big buildings.
I live in an apartment with a doorman.
And I can buy almost anything I want.
This isn't my life. It's just a glimpse.
Where's my real dad?
I don't know.
But don't worry.
He loves you, and I'm sure he'll be back very soon.
What are you doing?
They did a pretty good job.
Who did?
The aliens in the mother ship.
You look just like him.
Oh, thanks.
Slightly better looking though, right?
Oh, no, you're not gonna start crying, are you?
I don't think I could really deal with that right now.
Do you like kids?
On a case by case basis.
Do you know how to make chocolate milk?
I...I think I could figure it out.
Promise you won't kidnap me and my brother...
and plant stuff in our brains?
Sure.
Welcome to Earth.
This is where babies go when their parents are at work.
Check.
Just push the red button.
Do I get a receipt or something?
I have winter camping till 4:00
and ballet class until 5:30.
5:30. Okay.
And try not to be late...
'cause kids don't like to be the last one picked up.
Got it.
Good tip.
Bye.
Bye.
Hey, Annie.
Where do I go now?
Big Ed's.
Big Ed's Tires?
Why?
'Cause you work there.
You mean I sell tires.
That's what I do.
I'm a tire salesman.
Good Lord!
Morning, Jack.
Good morning, Jack.
Hey, Jack.
Jack, my boy.
Hey, guess who I played bridge with two nights ago.
Hell, you'll never guess. One Sydney Potter.
That's Sydney Potter, C.E.O., BuyRite Transport.
Only the third biggest trucking outfit in the state.
"Anyhoo" he's lookin' for a new parts supplier.
We can handle volume like that, now can't we, Jack?
I'm gonna have to get back to you on that, Ed.
Right on.
Excuse me. Do I...
do I have a private office somewhere in the building?
Sure, Jack.
Where is it?
It's...it's right back...right back there.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
You must've needed this every day.
What are you smiling about?
Eighty-eight?
I was in London in 1988.
You never went to London.
Jack
you're needed in mag wheels. Customer waiting.
I was the number one junior sales associate for E.F.Hutton in 1988.
Did you know that?
Uh, no. No, I didn't. That's great.
That's the kind of thing you could really build on, you know?
Yeah. I mean, sales has always been a feeder for M&A. Always.
Well, look, here we are.
The mag wheels. Mag wheels.
Hey, Jack, um, are you sure you're okay?
Well, I'm just a little confused right now about why I work here.
I just started here last Tuesday, so...
The closing tip was a mildly bullish plus-76.
Much of the market's action today was fueled by the latest round of merger mania...
to hit Wall Street...
when Global Health Systems and MedTech Pharmaceutical announced their intentions...
to join forces in a massive $122 billion stock swap deal
the largest ever in the health care industry.
When asked about the possible anti-competitive implications
Global chairman Bob Thomas referred reporters...
to P.K.Lassiter & Company president Alan Mintz, the architect behind the deal.
That's my deal!
Ironically, Mintz first met Thomas at a Lamaze class.
While coaching their pregnant wives, Mintz and Thomas...
struck up a dialogue, and two months later, the deal with MedTech was born.
He wasn't the architect! I'm the architect!
The kids are asleep.
The kids, hon. Honey.
Sweetheart
I said the kids are asleep.
That's just great. Those little monkeys can be a real handful.
Hey, I was watching that.
Not tonight.
Please leave my socks alone.
Wait. You want me.
That is the general idea, yeah.
Oh, well, maybe we should grab a bottle of wine first. Kind of break the ice.
Yeah, that's very funny. Look, it's 10:30.
By 11:00 you're gonna be snoring like a monster
but that's very sweet.
I'll remember that for next time.
Whatever you say...honey.
Oh, God, you're beautiful.
Thanks, Jack.
No, I'm serious.
You're really stunning.
This is good stuff. I want you to keep this up.
You were always a very pretty girl in college. There's no question about that.
But this...
You've really grown into a beautiful woman.
How can you do that?
What?
Look at me like you haven't seen me every day for the last 13 years.
Okay, wait. Don't move.
Don't look.
Stay right there.
I got something.
Good night, sweetheart.
Okay, we're almost out of here.
Mary Janes, Mommy. You promised.
That's right. I did promise. Okay. All right.
We're gonna stop at the kids' shoe department first
and then I gotta pick up my watch from the battery store.
Then I'm gonna go to the linen store.
Why don't we go to all the stores?
Every single store in this godforsaken shopping mall.
Wouldn't that be exciting?
You know what? Why don't I take the kids
and you just stay here and hang out in the men's department?
Come on, hon.
It's perfect for your frame.
Why don't you try it on?
I might want to take an inch out of the back.
Lengthen the sleeve.
You look amazing in that suit.
I mean, really...wow! Off the charts, great.
It's an unbelievable thing.
Wearing this suit actually makes me feel like a better person.
I'm gonna buy it.
It's $2,400.
Are you out of your mind?
Come on, let's go.
She got those shoes.
Those shoes were $25.
Come on. Take it off, all right?
We'll go to the food court and get one of those funnel cakes you like.
Daddy's a crazy guy.
No.
No.
Do you have any idea what my life is like?
Excuse me?
I wake up in the morning covered in dog saliva.
I drop the kids off
spend eight hours selling tires retail.
Retail, Kate.
I pick the kids up, walk the dog
which, by the way, carries the added bonus...
of carting away her monstrous crap.
I play with the kids, take out the garbage
get six hours of sleep if I'm lucky. Then everything starts all over again.
So what's in it for me?
Wh-where are my Mary Janes?
You know, it's sad to hear that your life is such a disappointment to you.
I can't believe it isn't a disappointment to you!
Jesus, Kate
I could have been a thousand times the man I became.
I could have been one of the richest Forbes...
How could you do this to me?
How could you let me give up on my dreams like this?
Really, I want to know.
Who are you?
All right, look. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was such a saint before...
and I'm such a prick now!
But maybe I'm just not the same guy that I was when we got married.
You know what? Maybe you're not.
Because the Jack Campbell I married would not need...
a $2,400 suit
to feel better about his life.
But I'm telling you, if that's what it's gonna take, then buy it.
Jesus! We'll take the money out of the kids'college fund.
Forget it.
We'll get a funnel cake.
It'll be the highlight of my week.
Listen, I'm really sorry about that back in the store.
I don't want to fight with you.
I just sometimes wonder how we ended up here, you know.
I mean, back in college, d-did you see us here?
Life has thrown us a few surprises. I'll give you that.
It really has, hasn't it?
Yeah. So, if you had to, what would you say was the biggest surprise?
Just out of curiosity. I'm just asking.
Well, Annie, for one.
Surprise, we're pregnant.
Yeah, that must have been. I mean, that...that was.
That was a very unexpected moment.
What are you gonna do?
I think it turned out all right, don't you?
Yeah. I really like Annie.
Well, good, Jack. Maybe we'll keep her.
No, I love her. I love Annie.
I'm just...
We had a lot of good times, didn't we?
Do you remember the place on Charles Street where we used to go?
Charles Street?
In the village?
When we were living in Greenwich Village.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Great times. Great place.
Why did we ever leave?
You can't really raise a kid in an apartment in the village.
Then there was the whole trek out to the hospital. That didn't help either.
You were great.
I mean, surviving the heart attack was one thing.
You had a heart attack?
Hey, Jack, stop that. 'Cause I am...I'm still mad at you.
Who knows what would have happened if you hadn't stepped in at the store?
That's why I work for Big Ed.
That's why I work for Big Ed.
Yeah.
So we had a baby, Big Ed had a heart attack.
Bought that house, and I've been workin' for him ever since.
Sayonara, Wall Street.
Our life in a nutshell.
If you want to look at it that way.
How would you look at it?
A great success story.
What do you say, Jack?
Show 'em how to do it, baby. Jack, we need a strike.
Damn!
Jesus, Jack. What are you doin'?
It's a league match.
Where's your follow through? Where's your stance?
You know what? I'm doin' the best I can.
It's okay, Jack. Why am I so competitive all the time?
You can still pick up that spare.
Crack 'em, Jack! Here we go. Hurt 'em.
You're Jack Campbell.
You're better than the sport.
You shot the rapids in Kanai.
You ran with the bulls in Pamplona.
You've jumped out of an airplane over the Mojave Desert, for Christ's sake.
You can do this. You can do this.
You can do this. You can do this.
Yes! Victorious!
Huh? All right!
High five!
You're up.
Go get 'em.
Hi, Jack.
Evelyn, right?
Very funny.
I saw you on lane 20.
You got the flu or something?
Something like that, yeah.
Need a nurse?
Are you a nurse?
If that's what you want.
Hey, wait a minute.
Um, don't run away.
Are we...
Are we what, Jack?
Well... Is there something going on between us?
Are we finally...
being honest?
It would help me if we were.
Okay. You're right. We've been dancing around this for years.
Here goes.
When I get dressed for a party, and I know you're gonna be there
let's just say I don't go strapless because my husband likes it.
I've got six sets of snow tires piled up in my garage
and I won't even drive in the snow.
And our kids just happen to be...
in the same ballet class every year.
So, if you're asking whether I'd like it to be more
the answer's yes.
Kate would never have to know.
Do I have your number?
Steve's out of town with the kids this weekend.
Why don't you just stop by?
Hey, Jack. You're all flushed.
I feel good.
Guess that 71 took a lot out of you.
No.
I just saw Evelyn Thompson.
She's relentless.
She wants to have an affair with me.
She said that?
Pretty much.
What is it about you?
So...if you would write her exact address down there. You have a pen? Please.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on a second.
You're not actually thinking about cheating on Kate?
Well, it wouldn't really be cheating, Arnie.
It's complicated.
Maybe I haven't been as good a consigliere as you've been to me
but hear me out on this.
A little flirtation is harmless
but you're dealing with fire here, man.
The Fidelity Bank and Trust is a tough creditor.
You make a deposit somewhere else, they close your account...
forever, all right?
Arnie, I don't want your head to explode
but I'm telling you, those rules don't apply to me.
I-I'm not even...
I'm not talking about rules. I'm talking about
Y-You're...
There isn't a guy in Union County who wouldn't give his left nut...
to be with Kate, all right?
She's amazing, and you're gonna fuck it up.
Just think about that, all right?
Hey, honey.
How was the game?
Long and boring and generally pretty sad.
Arnie seemed to enjoy it.
Sort of.
Hey, where's that chocolate cake?
Do you mean this chocolate cake?
That's my piece. I was saving it...
because I got nauseated by that precooked mini-mall rotisserie chicken.
It's good.
Give me that cake.
No way.
Come on.
I'm sorry. It's too important to me.
I want that cake!
You want this cake?
I want it.
Thank you.
It's good, right?
Are the kids asleep?
Say it to me, Jack.
What?
You know what I like to hear.
I know, baby. I know what you like to hear.
Tell me. Tell me, tell me.
You're a bad girl, baby. You make me so hot.
What?
Not it?
Nice, Jack.
Sweeping me off my feet.
You make me hot.
What do you say, everyone? This is a little birthday party for Katie.
Happy birthday, Katie.
Good to see you kids still together.
Hello, kids.
Evelyn, you look tremendous.
Look what happens when I do that.
Jack?
The man.
Do you have anything to say to your lovely wife on the day of her birth?
Hey, hey!
Today's your birthday?
That's funny, Jack.
You know what?
Wow, your birthday.
It's... You're my wife.
You are my wife. Today is your birthday.
Well, actually, I do have one thing that I want to say to you.
And God, I hope you like it.
Bill?
Oh, no.
Yes. You hit it, Bill.
You wore that shirt last year, by the way. Just so you know.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
There's love in the air.
He loves her. It's official. There's love.
Come on, it's time to get up, honey.
Good morning, Joshie.
Happy anniversary, honey.
Now, listen
before you do whatever crazy stunt you've got planned
I want you to open mine first.
Maybe I should wait.
No! Come on!
Come on, come on, come on. Open it.
Zeena?
I found it at an outlet store.
Look, I know it's a knockoff
but I think it's gonna look great on you.
Ah, enjoy it, sweetheart.
Yeah, uh...you're probably expecting something from me.
Here's the thing...
I hadn't really planned on giving you your anniversary gift...
until tonight.
You know, anniversary's good all day.
What are you talking about? You can never wait all day.
You can't even wait till it's light out. Come on!
I know.
I know. That's me. It's true.
And but...
it's funny...
You forgot.
You actually forgot our anniversary.
I'll fix it.
I'll go out right now and I'll get you something.
I'll make it right.
Let me know if there's enough chocolate in there, sweetheart.
Mm, not bad.
Good.
I should have warned you.
Dad always does something really special for the anniversary.
Like what?
One year he had a star named after her.
He had a star named after her?
Well, that's nice, but isn't that a little...
corny?
Mom liked it.
Maybe there's a jewelry store at the mall. I can pick her up a pair of earrings or something.
That's good, but...
you did forget the anniversary.
That's right. That is a major oversight.
Okay, okay. So, if I'm Kate
I can't afford the finer things.
My husband's career is definitely a crushing disappointment to me.
I'm trapped in suburbia.
Did he ever take her to the city?
Now you're getting the hang of it.
Jack, can we afford this place?
I'm taking my baby out for our anniversary. Damn the costs.
What do you want?
We'll have the Terrine of Quail Breast with Shiitake Mushrooms to start.
Then the Veal Medallions in Raspberry Truffle Sauce.
And the Sea Scallops with Pureed Artichoke Hearts.
Very good, sir.
And may I say, those are all excellent selections.
You may.
Also, we'll have a bottle of Lafite, '82.
Honey
that's an $800 bottle of wine.
We'll just have some red wine by the glass.
You are so not off the hook yet, Slick.
But I'm getting close, right?
You wanna dance?
I-I don't think there's dancing here, Jack.
Sure, there is. Come on.
Not bad for a tire salesman from New Jersey.
I have my moments.
You gotta try one of these.
God, I miss that taste.
I need to tell you something.
I think it may help us
but there's a slight chance it could make things worse.
I'm living someone else's...
I feel like I'm living someone else's life.
I remember I used to walk to work, and
I had a warm bialy in my hand
and a hot cup of coffee from Dean & Deluca
the crisp feeling of The Wall StreetJournal
the smell of leather from my briefcase.
I used to be so sure about everything, confident.
You know, I-I knew exactly who I was...
and what I wanted.
And then one morning, I woke up...
and suddenly it was all different.
Worse, do you mean?
No.
Well, maybe a few things
but mostly just different.
And it's okay.
But I never used to be like this, Kate.
I was the guy who had it all figured out.
I had no doubts. I had no regrets.
And now?
Now I don't. I don't have it all figured out.
Me neither.
But you always seem so certain.
Do you think there aren't mornings when I wake up and wonder, "What the hell am I doing in New Jersey?"
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
My office is a dump.
I answer my own phone, and you seen my paycheck.
Your paycheck is a disgrace to paychecks.
Can you imagine a life where everything was just easy?
You know, where you ask for things, and people just bring them to you?
It's wonderful.
I think about it too.
I do.
I wonder about what kind of life I would have had if I hadn't married you.
And?
Then I realize I've just erased all the things in my life that I'm sure about.
You...and the kids.
Good things.
What are you sure about?
I'm sure that right now there's nowhere else I'd rather be than here with you.
You like it?
This is beautiful.
You know champagne makes me do crazy things.
I'll just fill yours up to the top.
I don't know how you did it, Hoss, but you pulled it off.
I'm out of the doghouse?
Way out.
Happy anniversary, sweetheart.
You may even get lucky tonight, Jack.
You're so beautiful.
I already told you you were gonna get lucky.
My God.
All this time, I never stopped loving you.
That's all I wanted to hear.
I'm gonna wear the usual today.
What are you thinking? You want to come to work with Dad
help me sell tires? It's fun.
I'm pretty good at it. Who's this?
Who's that?
Who is that?
Who's on that tie?
That's Grandpa.
Have a great day.
For the money, this is hands down the best radial we carry.
Okay. I guess I'll take 'em.
You won't regret it. Tommy.
Would you set Mr.Collin up with four B.F.Goodrich G-Force T.A.'s?
Give him ten percent off for having the best costume.
Thank you.
You bet.
Right this way, sir. Follow me.
Tell me, does the tire smell good?
Remember our Valentine's Day special:
balance and alignment for free!
How are you doin' today?
It just blew out on me.
Do you have a tire like that?
I seem to have some sort of a blow out here.
Why don't you let me take this one, Kenny?
Okay, chief.
Peter Lassiter.
Do I know you?
Not exactly. I've seen you on CNBC.
You look taller in real life.
Truth is, Mintz was so busy timing his wife's breathing
he didn't realize that MedTech needed Global more than the other way around.
Ten days, two weeks tops, they would have approached you with an offer.
I'm willing to bet anything it would have been 130 billion
not 122.
The trouble is...
Peter, you had a pussycat running the show. What you needed was a Doberman.
I'm impressed.
I really am.
Now, about my car...
Sure.
We're gonna have to special order that tire, so it'll be ready in a couple of days.
All right.
This is...
my office address.
Why don't you drop off the car yourself?
We're really more of a boutique operation, as you can see.
But you're not interested in boutique dollars. I get it.
He's expecting you, Mr.Lassiter.
Alan
this is Jack Campbell
the one I was telling you about.
Of course. Jack.
Hi. Mr.Mintz.
No, just call me Alan. We like to cultivate a very casual atmosphere here.
I can see that.
What can I tell you? Do you have kids?
Uh, actually, yes.
Two of'em.
Good ones.
Great, great. Why don't you have a seat?
Peter mentioned to me that you're an avid CNBC watcher.
But he didn't say whether you had any actual Wall Street experience.
Um, I was a sales associate at E.F.Hutton.
A broker, really?
And now you're in the tire business?
That's right. And auto supply.
In the retail end, I understand.
We get about 60 percent of our business from automotive service.
And do you mind me asking what kind of sales you did in the last year?
Just ball park. We did 1.7 million in total revenue.
1.7. That's great.
And what do you project for this year?
I think we're gonna have a banner year.
Sales are up almost 20 percent in the first quarter
and we just landed a major trucking company account.
You did? That's great.
So that puts you just a tad over two million?
That's right.
And that would make us number one in our market.
Excuse me. I'm gonna get a glass of water.
Look
I know our paltry little $2 million in sales
is about what you spend a year on office supplies.
And some regional trucking company account is nothing compared to a multi-billion-dollar merger
No, no, no. I'm not trying to knock the tire business.
It's okay. I get it.
I'm in your shoes, I'm thinking the same thing, but...
here's the deal. Business is business. Wall Street, Main Street.
It's all a bunch of people getting up in the morning, trying to figure out how they're going to send their kids to college.
It's just people
and I know people.
I'm sure you do.
Take you, for instance, Alan.
You have a certain energy about you, an active kind of energy.
I wouldn't be surprised if you drank about 16 Diet Cokes a day.
You're an excellent father
but you feel guilty about the time you spend away from home.
You drink bourbon, but you offer your clients Scotch.
And your wife decorated this office.
He certainly seems to have your number.
You're a little tougher, Peter.
For one thing, you like expensive things.
That's easy.
You've seen my car.
You smoke Hoyo de Monterreys.
You're a Scotch man, single malt
not because it's trendy
but because you've been doing it for 40 years and you like to stay with what works.
You have two great loves in your life
your horses
and this company.
And you're a man who prides himself in finding talent in unusual places.
How would you know that?
Because I'm here.
I'm prepared to do whatever it takes to get this job.
I'll start wherever I have to start. I'll park cars if I have to.
The biggest part of judging character is knowing yourself
and I know this
I can do this job.
I can.
Give me a chance, Peter.
I won't let you down.
Alan
why don't you show Jack around?
This is our war room. We did seven major deals in here last year
three of them...hostile.
Yeah.
You get a kind of a feeling from...
Can we cut the shit here for a minute? Where did you get that information?
Did you go through his wallet? Did you surf some Net?
It doesn't really matter because that circus act you pulled back there...
may have dazzled Lassiter, but it doesn't cut any shit with me.
Even if you get this job, which I highly doubt, let me just give you a word of warning.
Peter Lassiter gets tired of his pet projects very, very quickly.
I've got that big office because I prove myself to him year after year after year.
Nobody is gonna come in here and turn the old man's head, especially not some tire salesman from New Jersey.
So if you're cautious and you're quiet
you watch yourself, stay away from Lassiter
maybe I'll think about keeping you on here after he gets bored with you.
Do we understand each other?
Alan!
God, you really are different.
Excuse me?
I mean, wow!
I'm impressed. I'm impressed.
Good for you.
Are we understanding each other?
Yes, Alan, I understand you.
Okay then.
Good.
Good.
Okay. Okay.
Keep your eyes closed. Hold on.
Go ahead. Open your eyes.
Welcome to Xanadu.
It's pretty incredible, isn't it?
It's like a museum.
Look around.
So what's the big surprise?
You didn't rent this for the weekend, did you?
Think...bigger.
For the week?
This place is a perk, Kate.
A perk?
For what?
A company called P.K.Lassiter Investment House...
uses it to attract new executives.
I'm going into arbitrage, honey.
It turns out I have a knack for it.
Jack, what are you talking about?
I'll be making twice what I make now, plus a hefty bonus.
That's just to start. And we can live in this apartment...
practically rent free...
until we find a place of our own.
Are you out of your mind?
I don't think so.
This is gonna be a better life for all of us. We can put Annie and Josh into private schools.
Annie goes to a great school, Jack.
I'm talking about the best schools in the country here.
What could you possibly be thinking about?
What about my job?
Well, this is New York City. It's like the needy people capital of the world.
Your Jersey clients aren't a tenth as pathetic as the ones you could find here.
I can't even believe you're talking about moving back into the city.
I thought the reason we left was because we didn't want to raise the kids here.
No. No.
This is the center of the universe.
If I were living in Roman times, I would live in Rome. Where else?
Today America is the Roman empire.
New York is Rome itself.
Jack!
Okay
you know something? I'm detecting, like, a funky tension here.
This was supposed to be a happy day, so guess what?
I don't need this.
We don't have to live here. Forget it.
I'll commute. I'll drive to work.
In traffic, it's over an hour each way.
That's three hours every day.
When are you ever going to see the kids?
Kate.
You're not understanding me.
I'm talking about a perfect life, a great life.
Everything we pictured when we were young. The whole package.
You said so yourself. Life has thrown us a few surprises.
We made sacrifices. Well, guess what?
Now I can finally get us back on track.
I can do that, Kate.
I want to do that.
I need to do that as a man!
For all of us.
Please just think about this for one second.
No more lousy restaurants.
No more clipping coupons.
No more shoveling snow.
Then get a goddamn snowblower, Jack!
Don't go get a new career without even telling me about it!
And don't...don't take Annie out of a school she loves.
Don't move us out of a house we've become a family in.
Don't you see?
I'm talking about us finally having a life...
that other people envy.
Oh, Jack.
They already do envy us.
From London to New York.
I came back.
When you got on that plane
I was sure it was over.
I left the airport afraid I'd never see you again.
And then you showed up the very next day.
That was a good surprise.
You know
I think about the decision you made.
Maybe I was being naive
but I believed that we would grow old together in this house
that we'd spend holidays here and...
have our grandchildren come visit us here.
I had this image of us all gray and wrinkly
and me...working in the garden
and you repainting the deck.
But things change.
If you need this, Jack
if you really need this
I will take these kids from a life they love
and I'll take myself from the only home we've ever shared together
and I'll move wherever you need to go.
I'll do that because I love you.
I love you
and that's more important to me than our address.
I choose us.
I'm gonna chase you.
You can't catch me.
No, you can't. You can't.
I fell down.
I knew you'd come back.
Annie.
I love you.
What are you doing?
Ringing my bell.
4.99? It's just salt, for God sakes.
Ninety-nine cents, darlin'.
Out of ten.
You.
Jack!
What's up? How you feeling, baby?
Why are you here?
Here's your change, darlin'.
Five, six, seven, eight
nine, oh-one.
Is that rock salt?
Look at you, man. Went and got all domestic and everything.
You really figured some things out, huh?
You're not sending me back.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Hey, did you hear me?
I'm talking to you.
You see that?
And for what, for nine bucks? That's just so disappointing.
I'm not going back.
You understand me?
Okay, relax, Jack.
You can't do this.
You can't keep coming in and out of people's lives, messing things up. It's not right.
A glimpse, by definition, is an impermanent thing, Jack.
I've got kids.
I'm goin' home.
Is it morning yet?
No, honey.
Go back to sleep.
Take care, Annie.
I'm going back to the mother ship.
These past few weeks...
I know I've done some...
some unusual things.
It's been interesting, that's for sure.
I've done some good things, too, though, haven't I?
You've been Jack Campbell
and that's always a good thing.
I need you to remember me, Kate.
How I am right now...
at this very moment.
I need you to put that image in your heart and keep it there.
Keep it with you no matter what happens.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Please just promise me.
You have to promise me, because if you don't, then it's like it never happened
and I don't think I can live with that.
I promise.
Promise me again.
I promise.
Okay.
Now come to bed.
Soon.
What time is it?
10:30.
Okay.
Waiting for me by the door, huh?
Paula.
Wow...
Merry Christmas.
Christmas?
It's not Christmas.
It's whatever you want it to be, Jack.
It's not Christmas.
Jack.
Jack?
Can I help you?
Is Kate here?
Does Kate live here?
Kate? No. There's nobody named Kate here.
Of course not.
You okay?
No.
Hello.
Santa Claus
where are you? Everybody's here.
Adelle?
You're a half an hour late.
The emergency strategy session, trip to Aspen?
Is this ringing any bells?
Everybody is panicked here, Jack.
Jack?
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
No, I'm not gonna go talk to them until I have something to talk to them about.
Steve, I don't care if it's Christmas day. We're in a crisis here.
Wait a minute. Jack just walked in. I'll call you back. Jack.
Thank God that you're...
You're here. Are you all right?
What's going on here?
What's...well, it's not good.
Bob Thomas has been talking to a European drug company, Jack
and we don't know which one.
They're gonna let Bob buy a minority stake
and let him keep running the entire company.
Global knows. I don't know how they know, but they know
and they're up in arms.
They think that somehow we should have been prepared for this. Prepared!
Oh, God, we're in trouble.
You know something, Alan?
Somewhere inside of you
there's a much more assertive person.
Is this another one of those Sun Tzu Art of War tricks?
No.
So what are we gonna do, Jack?
Jack?
I'll tell you exactly what we're going to do.
You're going to do whatever you have to do to find out...
which European company he's been talking to.
Then I'm going to clean myself up
fly to Aspen
and drink eggnog with Bob Thomas.
His wife and kids will be playing in the background in the snow...
while I convince him that the European company is the devil...
and Global is the answer to his prayers.
Then I'm gonna spend four hours skiing.
Alone.
Completely and utterly alone.
I'm going to do that because...
that is my life, that's what's real
and there's nothing I can do to change that.
For Manhattan.
Kate Reynolds.
I need an address too.
It's very fragile, so I want you to be very careful with it, okay?
It's valuable. It's over 300 years old.
You'll probably need a few guys to carry it. All right.
The painting is also very, very old, so take extra care.
It means a lot to Kate, okay? I appreciate it.
Yeah?
What?
Are you from the moving company?
I'm Jack Campbell.
I'm an old...friend of Kate's.
Kate, some guy is here.
Did you call the airline like I asked you to do?
Jack.
Kate.
God, it's been a long time.
You look...
You look great.
Thanks.
I...
Come on in. Come on in. I'm just doing some...
Lori, do you know where those boxes?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no! You know what... Jack. Don't... Please.
I don't even care.
Oh, great. Thank you.
What's going on?
I'm moving to Paris.
Hey, Lori
have you seen that box? It says "Jack" on it.
I put it with the rest of the Salvation Army stuff.
Do you want me to look for the box or call the airline, Kate?
Hey, kind of under a little pressure here.
Hey, kind of giving up Christmas day for my ex-boss here.
Hey, didn't mind offering to help when she was opening the Prada bag I gave her.
Maybe it's by the wardrobe boxes.
Thank you.
So you're moving.
Yeah, to Paris.
My firm has an office there. I'm gonna be heading it up.
Paris.
Paris, France?
That's the one.
So you're...you're not at a nonprofit firm?
God, no, not with what they pay me.
Are you married?
No, I never got married, Jack. You?
Not exactly.
Look, could we take a minute here, maybe go get a cup of coffee or something?
I'll go for a cup of coffee.
Yes. I found it.
Congratulations. Your earlier flight was cancelled
but I got you out of Kennedy on Dited at 7:00.
Excellent.
Am I good or what?
Yes, you're brilliant.
Here you go. It's just some old stuff of yours.
Do you ever think about us, Kate?
About what might have happened?
Jack, I'll tell you what.
If you're ever in Paris...
look me up and we'll go have that cup of coffee, okay?
Or cafe. Or cafe au lait.
Don't close that up. I will never find this box again.
Well, I marked it.
Just be more specific next time.
We'll leave it open then.
I was just trying to close it up.
Make a right here.
Sir, you're gonna be late for your flight.
We're not going to the airport.
You can't leave this here.
You can't park here!
Kate!
You can't go.
Don't get on that plane.
Please
let's just go have a cup of coffee. That's all I'm asking for.
I'm sure there's another flight to Paris tonight.
Jack.
What are you doing here?
Do you need closure?
Because if you do, after all these years
you got it. I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I...I was heartbroken, Jack
but I got over it, I moved on, and...
you should move on too.
Okay? I'm sorry. I just can't...
I've gotta go.
I-I...I'm sorry, Jack.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Can I just...I'm sorry. I was here.
We have a house in Jersey!
We have two kids.
Annie and Josh.
Annie's not much of a violin player, but she tries real hard.
She's a little precocious
but that's only because she says what's on her mind.
And when she smiles...
And Josh
he has your eyes.
He doesn't say much, but we know he's smart.
He's always got his eyes open.
You know, he's always watching us.
Sometimes
you can look at him and you just know...
he's learning something new.
It's like witnessing a miracle.
The house is a mess, but it's ours.
After 122 more payments, it's going to be ours.
And you...
you're a nonprofit lawyer.
That's right.
You're completely nonprofit.
But that doesn't seem to bother you.
And we're in love.
After 13 years of marriage, we're still unbelievably in love.
You won't even let me touch you till I've said it.
I sing to you.
Not all the time, but definitely on special occasions.
And we've
we've dealt with our share of surprises
and made a lot of sacrifices, but we stayed together.
You see
you're a better person than I am
and it made me a better person to be around you.
I don't know. Maybe...
maybe it was all just a dream.
Maybe I went to bed one lonely night in December and I imagined it all
but I swear, nothing's ever felt more real.
And if you get on that plane right now
it'll disappear forever.
I know we could both go on with our lives, and we'd both be fine.
But I've seen...
what we could be like together.
And I choose us.
Please, Kate.
One cup of coffee.
You can always go to Paris.
Just...
please
not tonight.
Okay, Jack.
Okay.

